RYAN ZADORECKY

2nd Year College Student in Learning

DuBois, PA 15801

namelessgamer74@gmail.com

(585)-729-7804

Entry-Level Front-End Web Developer. More than 2 years of general experience in HTML/CSS, about 6 months to a year each in JS and PHP, and in learning of mySQL. Works well with teams, and can handle a deadline within a team. Open to learning new languages during the job. Looking for an internship position in the field to get 150 hours of work in by april 2021.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer



WORK EXPERIENCE ----

Web Developer/Designer

September 2020 to December 2020

- This was a Mock Company for my School project
- Completely created and designed by myself, database stuff handled by 4 others

I Started the design by mocking it up in Adobe XD, and figured out how I could act on it. This was an Ecommerce site, so I had to come up with something simple, yet elegant, and still keep functionality.

- This was a website made from HTML/CSS, PHP, and some minor JS to help create the addition of items into the cart and add them into local storage
- This site taught me how budget out Time Management and what it's like to work on a strict deadline but still put out a solid product.
- This as well taught me what its like to work with a team, and what it means to take a role, and exceed at it.

Web Developer

January 2019 to June 2020

- This was another Mock Company for a personal project
- This site was mainly made of HTML and CSS, it was not very sophisticated.
- I as well mainly used this website for studying front end.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Sciences and Technologies

Penn State DuBois - DuBois, PA August 2019 to May 2023

High school diploma or GED

Holley Jr/Sr High - Holley, NY September 2016 to June 2019



SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Scripting
- · Web Development
- User Interface (UI)



ASSESSMENTS

Attention to Detail — Highly Proficient

November 2020

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: Highly Proficient

Programming Fundamentals — Familiar

November 2020

Designed by engineering managers and real-world employers, this test gives you hard data points to evaluate technical competency.

Full results: Familiar

Software Developer Fit — Familiar

November 2020

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers.

Full results: Familiar

Java — Familiar

November 2020

Designed by engineering managers & real-world employers, this Java test evaluates general technical competency. Full results: Familiar

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.